import { TrueOrFalseQuestionType } from "../../types";

export const trueOrFalseQuestion: TrueOrFalseQuestionType[] = [
  {
    id: "1",
    question: "Ron wears glasses.",
    correctAnswer: false,
  },
  {
    id: "2",
    question: "Harry's pet name is Hedwig.",
    correctAnswer: true,
  },
  {
    id: "3",
    question: "Harry likes chocolate.",
    correctAnswer: false,
  },
  {
    id: "4",
    question: "Ron's favorite game is chess.",
    correctAnswer: true,
  },
  {
    id: "5",
    question: "Ron has the trademark fiery red hair of the Weasley family.",
    correctAnswer: true,
  },
  {
    id: "6",
    question: "Harry doesnâ€™t like watching TV.",
    correctAnswer: false,
  },
  {
    id: "7",
    question: "Harry is taller than Ron.",
    correctAnswer: true,
  },
  {
    id: "8",
    question: "Ron is a bad friend.",
    correctAnswer: false,
  },
  {
    id: "9",
    question: "Harry was known for having a lightning bolt-shaped scar.",
    correctAnswer: true,
  },
  {
    id: "10",
    question: "Ron wants to be a teacher.",
    correctAnswer: false,
  },
];
